What would work be like if you had no boss?
要是没有老板，工作会是什么样子呢？
Imagine you could make all your own decisions and no one told you what to do.
想象一下，你可以自己做所有的决定，而且没有人会告诉你该做什么。
One company decided to find out if it could work.
有一家公司决定弄清楚这种情况是否可行。
The staff at Crisp, a Swedish software consultancy, chose to get rid of their CEO and create a completely flat organisation.
瑞典的一家软件咨询公司Crisp的员工们选择辞退他们的首席执行官，并创建一个完全扁平化的组织。
Having trialled several different management structures, the firm agreed to take the radical step of having no single leader.
在试用了几种不同的管理结构之后，这家公司决定采取这一激进的举措，即一个领导者都不要。
First, they needed to establish what a CEO actually did.
首先，他们需要确定一位CEO实际上都做些什么。
Then they shared those duties out amongst staff and board members.
然后，他们把这些职责分配给员工和董事会成员。
Employee Yassal Sundman told the BBC: “When we looked at it we had nothing left in the CEO column, and we said, ’all right, why don‘t we try it out?’”.
员工亚萨尔·桑德曼告诉英国广播公司：“当我们审视这些职责时，我们发现CEO那一栏里没有剩下任何内容了，于是我们说，‘好吧，我们为什么不试一试呢？’”
Which is exactly what they did.
他们确实这么做了。
And Crisp employee, Heinrich Kniberg, believes it‘s been a good move.
而且Crisp公司的员工海因里克·克尼伯格认为这是一个不错的举措。
He says the company can now act faster: “If you want to get something done, you stand up and start driving that”.
他说公司现在行动速度更快了：“如果你想做成某件事，你就站起来，开始推动这件事。”
Kniberg also claims workers are more motivated.
克尼伯格还声称员工们更有主动积极性了。
Crisp regularly measures staff satisfaction, and say they average over four out of five.
Crisp公司定期调查员工的满意度，并且表示满意度平均超过了五分之四。
Any big decisions are made during the company-wide four-day meetings several times a year.
任何重大决策都是在每年几次的为期四天的全公司会议上做出的。
They do still have a board: it‘s a legal requirement.
他们确实仍然设有董事会：这是法律要求。
But the board can be used as a last resort to resolve tricky issues.
但董事会可以作为解决棘手问题的最后手段。
So, if it’s working out for Crisp, could this model become more widespread?
那么，如果这种模式对Crisp公司有效，它能更广泛地推广吗？
Online retailer Zappos tried out a similar plan but had mixed results.
在线零售商Zappos尝试了一个类似的计划，但结果喜忧参半。
Almost a fifth of Zappos staff decided to leave, and chief executive Tony Hsieh admitted that “self-management is not for everyone”.
几乎五分之一的Zappos员工决定离职，首席执行官托尼·谢承认“自我管理并不适合每个人”。
Founder of file-sharing service Dropbox, Drew Houston, believes that a leaderless structure is too chaotic.
文件共享服务公司Dropbox的创始人德鲁·休斯顿认为，没有领导者的结构太混乱了。
“Often infinite freedom like that can be pretty disorientating.
休斯顿先生说：“像那样的无限自由常常会让人非常迷茫。
It doesn‘t always feel good, because you no longer know what you‘re supposed to do, what’s important and you‘re bumping up against other people,” Mr Houston says.
这种感觉并不总是好的，因为你不再知道自己该做什么，什么是重要的，而且你还会与其他人产生冲突。”
So, what is the perfect balance?
那么，什么才是完美的平衡呢？
How do you keep accountability in a company without hierarchy?
在没有等级制度的公司里，要如何保持责任心呢？
Would you like to work somewhere with no boss?
你愿意在一个没有老板的地方工作吗？